KAI DE TAN

Blockchain, Full-stack developer toptall.cook@gmail.com

Accomplished IT professional with 7+ years of experience in solution design, architecture, and application development in web and Android / iPhone or client environments. Record of success in leading projects that have increased revenue, as well as savings. Well-versed in software development life cycle and skilled architect. Recognized for ability to lead, build relationships with key personnel and complete projects on time. Exceptional developer with skills to create, design, and implement enterprise solutions for clients.

EXPERIENCE

JANUARY 2021 -

BLOCK CHAIN DEVELOPER, FREELANCING

While studying blockchain, I worked in several projects related to blockchain.

- Developed DeFi farming platform pro.goonus.io as a frontend and web3 developer. (React, Web3)
- Built NFT monitoring web platform whale watcher as a frontend and web3 developer. (Vue, Web3)

https://www.cryptokitties.co/

https://pro.goonus.io/

https://app.nansen.ai/

https://www.bandprotocol.com/

https://www.socios.com/

NOVEMBER 2017 – JUNE 2020

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER, TYPENT

- Developed some Ecommerce sites using HTML/CSS, JavaScript, WordPress, Shopify and
- Very Clean and Neat Designing and making a LIVE Website from Figma with React.js as much as working very efficient and less time-consuming.
- Database, API integrations, Payments Integrations using PayPal / Stripe / Authorize.net and 2checkout, data analysis, Twilio, MailChimp, SES, Klaviyo and Zoho integrations etc.

https://shopmarthas.com/

https://www.manitobah.com/

https://www.hellofresh.com/

https://www.bagamour.com/

JANUARY 2017 - NOVEMBER 2017

FRONT-END DEVELOPER, BLITZ GG LOS ANGELES, CALIFORNIA

Developing Blitz.gg website using ReactJS and NodeJS

- The personal gaming coach for League of Legends, Valorant, CSGO, Fortniteand more powered by AI and built with professional players.
- I developed whole web pages using React and Styled-components.
- Adding several types of analytics and Advertising.

AUGUST 2016 - JANUARY 2017

FRONT-END DEVELOPER, OCTAL INFO SOLUTION

Maintained an eagerness to add to my knowledge and skills.

Functioned with flexibility and agility.

Worked on creating Single Page application (SPA) using AngularJS, HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap &

Created webpages according to client's guidelines and standards throughout the development and maintenance of the website using HTML, XHTML, CSS and JavaScript.

https://www.shiftwizard.com/

https://www.youngmoorelaw.com/

https://tischbraintumorcenter.duke.edu/

EDUCATION

SEPTEMBER 2012- JULY 2016

BACHELOR IN COMPUTER SCIENCE, SINGAPORE INSTITUDE OF TECHNOLOGY

Operating System Architecture, Data Structure and Algorithms, Software Engineering & Quality Assurance, Signal and Processing, Digital Circuit, Embedded System, AI & System Design, Relational Database Design, Network & Communication

KEY SKILLS

- Good time management skills, prioritization skills
- Clear and effective communication skills
- Superior attention to detail
- Able to meet tight deadlines
- Innovative, always full of new ideas & suggestions

THECNIQUE

- Programming Languages : JavaScript, HTML, CSS, SQL, C++, Python, JAVA
- Database : MySQL, MongoDB
- MEAN Stack : MongoDB, Node.js, Angular, Express.js
- Ecommerce : WooCommerce, EC-CUBE, Shopify
- Web Service : REST, JSON, Firebase, SEO, Google Cloud
- MVC Framework: CodeIgnitor, Laravel, Zend, CakePHP
- Blockchain: Web3, Solidity, Python
- Smart Phone Stack: Kotlin, Android, Objective-C, Swift
- Hybrid Stack : Xamarin, C#

c/c++ Programming



MERN



PHP



Javascript



MongoDB



Mysql



Model-view-Controller

Solidity



Rust



Web3js



Teamwork



Communication



Problem Solving



LANGUAGES

ENGLISH ADVANCED CHINESE NATIVE